<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array
        name="easy">
        <item>Australia</item>
        <item>Brazil</item>
        <item>Canada</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Cuba</item>
        <item>England</item>
        <item>France</item>
        <item>Germany</item>
        <item>Israel</item>
        <item>Italy</item>
        <item>Jamaica</item>
        <item>Japan</item>
        <item>Korea</item>
        <item>Mexico</item>
        <item>Russia</item>
        <item>Spain</item>
        <item>Switzerland</item>
        <item>Turkey</item>
        <item>United Kingdom</item>
        <item>United States</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="medium">
        <item>Argentina</item>
        <item>Austria</item>
        <item>Belarus</item>
        <item>Belgium</item>
        <item>Bulgaria</item>
        <item>Bolivia</item>
        <item>Bosnia</item>
        <item>Chile</item>
        <item>Colombia</item>
        <item>Costa Rica</item>
        <item>Croatia</item>
        <item>Czech Republic</item>
        <item>Denmark</item>
        <item>Finland</item>
        <item>Greece</item>
        <item>Hungary</item>
        <item>Iceland</item>
        <item>India</item>
        <item>Iran</item>
        <item>Iraq</item>
        <item>Ireland</item>
        <item>Macedonia</item>
        <item>New Zealand</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>Nigeria</item>
        <item>Norway</item>
        <item>Peru</item>
        <item>Poland</item>
        <item>Portugal</item>
        <item>Romania</item>
        <item>Saudi Arabia</item>
        <item>Serbia</item>
        <item>Sweden</item>
        <item>Uruguay</item>
        <item>Ukraine</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="hard">
        <item>Afghanistan</item>
        <item>Albania</item>
        <item>Algeria</item>
        <item>Andorra</item>
        <item>Angola</item>
        <item>Anguilla</item>
        <item>Antigua and Barbuda</item>
        <item>Armenia</item>
        <item>Azerbaijan</item>
        <item>Bahamas</item>
        <item>Bahrain</item>
        <item>Bangladesh</item>
        <item>Barbados</item>
        <item>Belize</item>
        <item>Benin</item>
        <item>Botswana</item>
        <item>Brunei</item>
        <item>Burkina Faso</item>
        <item>Burma</item>
        <item>Burundi</item>
        <item>Cambodia</item>
        <item>Cameroon</item>
        <item>Cape Verde</item>
        <item>Central African Republic</item>
        <item>Chad</item>
        <item>Comoros</item>
        <item>Congo</item>
        <item>Cyprus</item>
        <item>Dominica</item>
        <item>Dominican Republic</item>
        <item>Ecuador</item>
        <item>Egypt</item>
        <item>El Salvador</item>
        <item>Equatorial Guinea</item>
        <item>Eritrea</item>
        <item>Ethiopia</item>
        <item>Fiji</item>
        <item>Gabon</item>
        <item>Gambia</item>
        <item>Georgia</item>
        <item>Ghana</item>
        <item>Gibraltar</item>
        <item>Grenada</item>
        <item>Guam</item>
        <item>Guatemala</item>
        <item>Guinea Bissau</item>
        <item>Guinea</item>
        <item>Guyana</item>
        <item>Haiti</item>
        <item>Vatican</item>
        <item>Honduras</item>
        <item>Hong Kong</item>
        <item>Indonesia</item>
        <item>Ivory Coast</item>
        <item>Bhutan</item>
        <item>Djibouti</item>
        <item>Greenland</item>
        <item>Jersey</item>
        <item>Montenegro</item>
        <item>Panama</item>
        <item>Senegal</item>
        <item>Syria</item>
        <item>Jordan</item>
        <item>Kazakhstan</item>
        <item>Kenya</item>
        <item>Kuwait</item>
        <item>Kyrgyzstan</item>
        <item>Laos</item>
        <item>Latvia</item>
        <item>Lebanon</item>
        <item>Lesotho</item>
        <item>Liberia</item>
        <item>Libya</item>
        <item>Liechtenstein</item>
        <item>Lithuania</item>
        <item>Luxembourg</item>
        <item>Macau</item>
        <item>Madagascar</item>
        <item>Malawi</item>
        <item>Malaysia</item>
        <item>Maldives</item>
        <item>Mali</item>
        <item>Malta</item>
        <item>Marshall Islands</item>
        <item>Mauritania</item>
        <item>Mauritius</item>
        <item>Micronesia</item>
        <item>Moldova</item>
        <item>Monaco</item>
        <item>Mongolia</item>
        <item>Montserrat</item>
        <item>Morocco</item>
        <item>Mozambique</item>
        <item>Namibia</item>
        <item>Nauru</item>
        <item>Nepal</item>
        <item>New Caledonia</item>
        <item>Nicaragua</item>
        <item>Niger</item>
        <item>Niue</item>
        <item>North Korea</item>
        <item>Oman</item>
        <item>Pakistan</item>
        <item>Palau</item>
        <item>Papua New Guinea</item>
        <item>Paraguay</item>
        <item>Philippines</item>
        <item>Puerto Rico</item>
        <item>Qatar</item>
        <item>Rwanda</item>
        <item>Saint Helena</item>
        <item>Saint Kitts and Nevis</item>
        <item>Saint Lucia</item>
        <item>Saint Martin</item>
        <item>Saint Pierre and Miquelon</item>
        <item>Saint Vincent and the Grenadines</item>
        <item>Samoa</item>
        <item>San Marino</item>
        <item>Sao Tome and Principe</item>
        <item>Seychelles</item>
        <item>Sierra Leone</item>
        <item>Singapore</item>
        <item>Slovakia</item>
        <item>Slovenia</item>
        <item>Solomon Islands</item>
        <item>Somalia</item>
        <item>South Africa</item>
        <item>South Georgia</item>
        <item>Sri Lanka</item>
        <item>Sudan</item>
        <item>Suriname</item>
        <item>Swaziland</item>
        <item>Taiwan</item>
        <item>Tajikistan</item>
        <item>Tanzania</item>
        <item>Thailand</item>
        <item>Timor Leste</item>
        <item>Togo</item>
        <item>Tonga</item>
        <item>Trinidad and Tobago</item>
        <item>Tunisia</item>
        <item>Turkmenistan</item>
        <item>Tuvalu</item>
        <item>Uganda</item>
        <item>United Arab Emirates</item>
        <item>Uzbekistan</item>
        <item>Vanuatu</item>
        <item>Venezuela</item>
        <item>Vietnam</item>
        <item>Virgin Islands</item>
        <item>Yemen</item>
        <item>Zambia</item>
        <item>Zimbabwe</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="easy_facts">
        <item>Australia is the sixth largest nation after Russia,
            Canada, China, the United States of America and Brazil. It
            has, however, a relatively small population.</item>
        <item>Brazil is the largest country in South America.</item>
        <item>Canada has more lakes than the rest of the world combined.
        </item>
        <item>If China imported just 10%% of it\'s rice needs- the price
            on the world market would increase by 80%%.</item>
        <item>Cuba is home to over 11 million people and is the most
            populous island nation in the Caribbean.</item>
        <item>Nearly 84%% of the population of the UK lives in England,
            mainly in the major cities and metropolitan areas.</item>
        <item>Nearly 20%% of the territory of France lies outside
            Europe. These regions are known as "DOM-TOM" (overseas
            departments and territories), where over 2.5 million French
            citizens live.</item>
        <item>Germany is Europe\'s second largest populous nation. It is
            also Europe\'s largest economy.</item>
        <item>Israel has the highest ratio of university degrees to the
            population in the world.</item>
        <item>The colors of the Italian flag represent the three
            cardinal virtues: Green - hope; White - faith; Red -
            charity.</item>
        <item>Christopher Columbus was the first European to visit
            Jamaica in 1494 and called it "the fairest island that eyes
            have beheld."</item>
        <item>More than a thousand earthquakes hit Japan every year.
            Japan also has about 200 volcanoes, 60 of which are active.
        </item>
        <item>South Korea has one of the strongest economies in Eastern
            Asia. Most of its wealth comes from manufacturing and
            service industries, such as banking. It exports ships, cars,
            computers, and other electronic items.</item>
        <item>Mexico\'s ancient societies built great cities and huge
            pyramids, created remarkable works of art, and even studied
            the stars and planets to determine when to plant crops and
            hold ceremonies.</item>
        <item>Russia, the largest country in the world, occupies
            one-tenth of all the land on Earth. It spans 11 time zones
            across two continents (Europe and Asia) and has coasts on
            three oceans (the Atlantic, Pacific, and Arctic).</item>
        <item>Spaniards are known for their love of life and for eating
            and drinking with family and friends. Traditional appetizers
            like tapas or pintxos, the Basque country equivalent, are
            popular. Regional dances and music are almost as important
            as soccer and religious festivals.</item>
        <item>Switzerland has one of the lowest crime rates of all
            industrialised countries.</item>
        <item>Turkey is home to one of the earliest settlements in the
            world. Built 8,800 years ago, Catal Hoyuk was a labyrinth of
            150 mud homes joined together. There were no streets in
            between, so people had to enter the homes through holes in
            the roof!</item>
        <item>The United Kingdom, also called the U.K., consists of a
            group of islands off the northwest coast of Europe. It is a
            unique country made up of four nations: England, Wales,
            Scotland, and Northern Ireland. England, Wales, and Scotland
            also make up Great Britain.</item>
        <item>The United States consumes 25%% of all the world\'s
            energy.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="medium_facts">
        <item>Argentina is a vast country located in the southern part
            of South America. The eighth largest country in the world,
            it is the second largest country in South America after
            Brazil, and it\'s about one-third the size of the United
            States.</item>
        <item>Austria is one of the most forested countries in Europe
            with almost half its territory covered in forest—and
            forested area is increasing steadily thanks to Austria\'s
            "green lung" projects.</item>
        <item>Much of Belarus (formerly the Belorussian Soviet Socialist
            Republic of the USSR, and then Byelorussia) is a hilly
            lowland with forests, swamps, and numerous rivers and lakes.
            There are wide rivers emptying into the Baltic and Black
            seas. Its forests cover over one-third of the land and its
            peat marshes are a valuable natural resource.</item>
        <item>There are over 800 kinds of beers made in Belgium.
            Belgians consume in average 150 liters of beer per person
            per year.</item>
        <item>The name Bulgaria has been kept after Bulgar people, who
            arrived here in the late seventh century.</item>
        <item>Bolivia has had more than 190 revolutions and coups since
            it became independent in 1825. The latest constitution was
            adopted in 1967.</item>
        <item>Bosnia and Herzegovina make up a triangular-shaped
            republic, about half the size of Kentucky, on the Balkan
            peninsula.</item>
        <item>About 40 percent of the Chile\'s population lives in the
            area around the capital of Santiago. Children in rural areas
            need to wake up at 5:00 - 6:00 am to walk to school or meet
            the bus. Their journeys sometimes take two hours each way.
        </item>
        <item>Colombia is nicknamed the "gateway to South America"
            because it sits in the northwestern part of the continent
            where South America connects with Central and North America.
        </item>
        <item>Costa Rica is a little country which is often called the
            "Switzerland of Central America". In 2009 Costa Rica was
            named the happiest country among all Americas (Northern,
            Central, and Southern).</item>
        <item>In Croatia, people can start voting at the age of 16, if
            they have a job, but have to wait until they turn 18, if
            they are unemployed.</item>
        <item>The Czech capital, Prague, is more than 1 000 years old
            and has a wealth of historic architecture of different
            styles. Because of this, the city has become a favoured
            location for many international film makers.</item>
        <item>In Denmark, it rains every second day. On average, a year
            has 171 days with a precipitation of more than 0.1mm). In
            2007, however, there were 188 days of precipitation.</item>
        <item>Finland is ranked as the least corrupt country in the
            world.</item>
        <item>The colors of the Flag Blue and White symbolize the blue
            of the Hellenic Sea and the Whiteness of its restless waves.
        </item>
        <item>Hungary is one of the oldest countries in Europe, founded
            way back in the year 896.</item>
        <item>Iceland has vast amounts of water because it rains so
            much. Icelandic water is so clean and pure that it is piped
            into the city and to the kitchen taps in the home without
            any treatment (no chlorination needed).</item>
        <item>With a population of over 1 billion, India is home to 400
            million children, the largest number in any country in the
            world.</item>
        <item>The former name of Iran was Persia, which was in use till
            1935. The word Iran means the ‘Land of the Aryan’s.</item>
        <item>Iraq occupies the ancient region of Mesopotamia, "land
            amidst the rivers," a fertile lowland created by the Tigris
            and Euphrates Rivers.</item>
        <item>Dublin, Ireland\'s capital was founded by the Vikings in
            988 and was originally called Dubh Linn (which means Black
            Pool in Irish).</item>
        <item>The landlocked and mostly mountainous country of
            Macedonia, in southeastern Europe, proclaimed independence
            from Yugoslavia in September 1991.</item>
        <item>Maoris were the first inhabitants of New Zealand, arriving
            on the islands in about 1000. Maori oral history maintains
            that the Maoris came to the island in seven canoes from
            other parts of Polynesia.</item>
        <item>The Dutch have a saying: "God made the Earth, but the
            Dutch made Holland." The first defenses against the sea went
            up some 800 years ago. Today more than 2,400 kilometers
            (1,491 miles) of dikes shield the low, flat land—almost half
            of which lies below sea level—from invasion by the North
            Sea.</item>
        <item>Nigeria is the most populous country in Africa, the eighth
            most populous country in the world, and the most populous
            country in the world in which the majority of the population
            is black.</item>
        <item>Norway has some of the highest petrol prices in the world,
            even though the country is one of the biggest oil exporter
            in the world.</item>
        <item>Peru is the home of the oldest civilizations in the world
            which was the Norte Chico civilization.</item>
        <item>Poland is the 6th most populous and the 6th largest of the
            27 member states in the European Union.</item>
        <item>Portugal is the oldest country in Europe to have its
            borders defined just as they are now.</item>
        <item>Romania lies on the Black Sea coast of southeastern
            Europe. The Carpathian Mountains and the Transylvanian Alps
            divide the country into three physical and historical
            regions: Wallachia in the south, Moldavia in the northeast,
            and Transylvania in the country\'s center.</item>
        <item>Saudi Arabia is keeper of Islam’s most sacred cities:
            Mecca, where the Prophet Muhammad received the word of
            Allah.</item>
        <item>The Kingdom of Serbia was formed in 1918, changing its
            name to Yugoslavia a decade later. In 1989, Slobodan
            Milosevic, new president of the Serbian Republic, called for
            Serbian domination, which led to the breakup of Yugoslavia.
        </item>
        <item>Sweden is the 3rd largest EU country in land area, after
            France and Spain.</item>
        <item>The world\'s first constitution was created by a Ukrainian
            politician Pylyp Orlyk. On April 5th, 1710.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array
        name="hard_facts">
        <item>Afghanistan was settled around 7000 B.C. and has been in
            transition for most of its history.</item>
        <item>Albania is one of the poorest countries in Europe (and the
            only one with a Muslim majority).</item>
        <item>Algeria is the second largest country in Africa. Over 1
            million Algerians died during the country\'s fight for
            independence from France which they achieved in 1962.</item>
        <item>Andorra\'s capital, Andorra la Vella, is the highest
            capital city in Europe, being at an elevation of 1023
            meters.</item>
        <item>Portuguese colony since the 15th century, Angola was the
            source for millions of slaves sent to Brazil and other
            places across the Atlantic.</item>
        <item>Anguilla\'s total land area of the territory is 91 km2
            with a population of approximately 13,500.</item>
        <item>Antigua and Barbuda, small islands in the eastern
            Caribbean, were colonized by the English in 1632. Sugar
            plantations ruled the economy, and African slaves were
            brought in as laborers.</item>
        <item>The Kingdom of Armenia was the first state to adopt
            Christianity as its religion, in the early years of the 4th
            century.</item>
        <item>Azerbaijan Democratic Republic was the first successful
            attempt to establish a democratic and secular republic in
            the Muslim world.</item>
        <item>Bahamas is an archipelago nation of approximately 700
            islands, of which 40 are populated. The islands cover an
            area of about 100,000 square miles.</item>
        <item>Bahrain is a small island country with approximately
            800,000 inhabitants (2009), located near the western shores
            of the Persian Gulf and ruled by the Al Khalifa royal
            family.</item>
        <item>Bangladesh is the eighth most populous country and is
            among the most densely populated countries in the world. The
            country also has a high poverty rate. However, per-capita
            (inflation-adjusted) GDP has more than doubled since 1975,
            and the poverty rate has fallen by 20%% since the early
            1990s.</item>
        <item>Once a Spanish and Portuguese territorial possession known
            as Los Barbados, in 1625 it became an English, and later a
            British, colony.Barbados has an estimated population of
            284,589 people, with around 80,000 living in or around
            Bridgetown, the largest city and the country\'s capital.
        </item>
        <item>Close to 1 million tourists visit Belize annually, 70%% of
            whom are Americans.</item>
        <item>Benin covers an area of approximately 110,000 square
            kilometers (42,000 sq mi), with a population of
            approximately 9.05 million. Benin is a tropical, sub-Saharan
            nation, highly dependent on agriculture, with substantial
            employment and income arising from subsistence farming.
        </item>
        <item>Botswana is slightly smaller than the US state of Texas.
            It mainly deals in diamonds and cattle. 70%% of Botswana is
            desert and the vast majority of its estimated 1.6 million
            population live along the banks of the river Okavango.
        </item>
        <item>Brunei won its independence in 1984 after almost a century
            as a British protectorate. Rich in oil and natural gas, the
            people of this Muslim sultanate enjoy high subsidies and
            generous health care. Brunei has an absolute monarchy and a
            hereditary nobility, with the sultan awarding titles to
            commoners.</item>
        <item>Burkina Faso\'s size is 274,200 square kilometers with an
            estimated population of more than 15,757,000.Formerly called
            the Republic of Upper Volta, it was renamed on August 4,
            1984, by President Thomas Sankara to mean "the land of
            upright people".</item>
        <item>Burma officially the Republic of the Union of Myanmar was
            part of Britain\'s Indian Empire until 1937, when it became
            a self-governing colony. Burma gained its independence from
            Britain in 1948.</item>
        <item>Burundi is one of the ten poorest countries in the world.
            It has the lowest per capita GDP of any nation in the world.
            Burundi\'s main exports include coffee and sugar.</item>
        <item>Cambodia is a country in Southeast Asia that borders
            Thailand to the west and northwest, Laos to the northeast,
            Vietnam to the east, and the Gulf of Thailand to the
            southwest. The geography of Cambodia is dominated by the
            Mekong River (Tonlй Mйkong) and Tonlй Sap lake.</item>
        <item>Cameroon is home to over 200 different linguistic groups
            and that is why it is known as ‘Africa in miniature’.
            Cameroon\'s population at 19,522,000 and it has a high level
            of religious freedom and diversity.</item>
        <item>The Republic of Cape Verde is an island country, spanning
            an archipelago of 10 islands located in the central Atlantic
            Ocean, 570 kilometers off the coast of Western Africa.
        </item>
        <item>Deep in the heart of the continent, the Central African
            Republic was part of French Equatorial Africa before
            independence in 1960. It is one of the world\'s least
            developed countries, with most of the population engaged in
            subsistence farming.</item>
        <item>Chad is about 85%% the size of Alaska. Its neighbors are
            Niger, Libya, the Sudan, the Central African Republic,
            Cameroon, and Nigeria. Lake Chad, from which the country
            gets its name, lies on the western border with Niger and
            Nigeria. In the north is a desert that runs into the Sahara.
        </item>
        <item>At 1,862 km2 (719 sq mi) the Comoros is the third-smallest
            African nation by area. With a population estimated at
            798,000, it is the sixth-smallest African nation by
            population although it has one of the highest population
            densities in Africa.</item>
        <item>The Congo is situated in west-central Africa astride the
            equator. It borders Gabon, Cameroon, the Central African
            Republic, the Democratic Republic of the Congo, and the
            Angola exclave of Cabinda, with a short stretch of coast on
            the South Atlantic. Its area is nearly three times that of
            Pennsylvania. Most of the inland is tropical rain forest,
            drained by tributaries of the Congo River.</item>
        <item>Cyprus gained independence in 1960. The country had
            previously been controlled by Great Britain and joined the
            British Commonwealth in 1961, meaning that Cyprus sends a
            team to the Commonwealth Games every four years.</item>
        <item>Dominica officially the Commonwealth of Dominica, is an
            island nation in the Caribbean Sea. Its size is 750 square
            kilometers and has an estimated population of 72,500.</item>
        <item>The Dominican Republic has more than 9 million people.It
            shares the island of Hispaniola in the Caribbean with the
            nation of Haiti, once served as a Spanish colony. Spanish is
            the primary language.</item>
        <item>Ecuador\'s name comes from the Equator, which divides it
            unequally, putting most of the country in the Southern
            Hemisphere. It may be the smallest Andean country, but it
            has four distinct and contrasting regions.</item>
        <item>Egypt is The world\'s original tourist destination, the
            seat of thought and influence in the Arab world and the
            first Arab country to make peace with Israel.</item>
        <item>El Salvador is the smallest but most densely populated
            country in Central America. Located between Guatemala and
            Honduras, it also has over 300 km of coastline on the North
            Pacific Ocean.</item>
        <item>Equatorial Guinea with an area of 28,000 square kilometers
            (11,000 sq mi) it is one of the smallest countries in
            continental Africa. It is also the most prosperous however,
            the wealth is concentrated in government and elite hands.
        </item>
        <item>Eritrea is a country in the Horn of Africa. The capital is
            Asmara. Eritrea\'s size is approximately 117,600 km2 (45,406
            sq mi) with an estimated population of 5 million.</item>
        <item>Ethiopia is the birthplace of coffee and they have
            official coffee ceremonies in the home. If you are offered
            coffee, it is very rude to decline.</item>
        <item>Fiji Islands is an archipelago that consists of 322
            islands and 522 smaller islets, lying in the Pacific Ocean,
            not far from Australia and New Zealand. Kayaking, rainforest
            treks, mountain biking, snorkeling and diving along with
            lush green surroundings and fabulous sea-bed offered by this
            dreamy island fulfills every visitor’s desire of having a
            matchless holiday.</item>
        <item>Gabon covers a land area of nearly 270,000 kmІ and has an
            estimated population of 1,500,000. Its capital and largest
            city is Libreville.</item>
        <item>Gambia is the smallest country on mainland Africa. Its
            size is almost 10,500 kmІ with an estimated population of
            1,700,000.</item>
        <item>Georgia contains two de facto independent regions,
            Abkhazia and South Ossetia, which Georgia considers to be
            occupied by Russia.</item>
        <item>Ghana is a big country but not the biggest in Africa, it
            is around the size of Great Britain. The word Ghana means
            Warrior King and was the title awarded to the kings of the
            medieval West African Ghana Empire.</item>
        <item>Gibraltar was listed as the 5th most stable and prosperous
            British Territory, in a one-year investigation of 235
            countries and territories. It is a peninsula of 6.843 square
            kilometers and home to almost 30,000 Gibraltarians and other
            nationalities.</item>
        <item>Grenada is an island country and Commonwealth Realm
            consisting of the island of Grenada and six smaller islands
            at the southern end of the Grenadines in the southeastern
            Caribbean Sea. Its size is 344 square kilometers (133 sq
            mi), with an estimated population of 110,000.</item>
        <item>There are men in Guam whose full-time job is to travel the
            countryside and deflower young virgins, who pay them for the
            privilege of having sex for the first time.Reason: under
            Guam law, it is expressly forbidden for virgins to marry.
        </item>
        <item>Almost all of the Guatemala Indians are descendents of the
            Mayan Culture. They live in towns or small settlements
            scattered across the country. Each of these groups has
            developed customs and colorful costumes in their communities
            that are totally individual and separate from each other.
        </item>
        <item>The Republic of Guinea-Bissau is a country in West Africa.
            It covers 36,125 kmІ (nearly 14,000 sq mi) with an estimated
            population of 1,600,000. Only 14%% of the population speaks
            the official language, Portuguese.</item>
        <item>Guinea\'s 10 million people belong to twenty-four ethnic
            groups. The most prominent groups are the Fula, Mandinka,
            and Susu.</item>
        <item>Guyana is a sovereign state on the northern coast of South
            America that is culturally part of the Anglophone Caribbean.
            Guyana has been a former colony of the British, Dutch,
            French and for 200 years the Spanish.</item>
        <item>Even BEFORE the earthquake, 1 in every 3 of Haiti’s kids
            die before the age of 5 years.</item>
        <item>Honduras is the poorest nation in Central America.
            Campesinos or farmers work plots of land and live in rural
            areas made up of small villages. Approximately half of all
            the adults are illiterate even though by law, children must
            attend school until the age of 15.</item>
        <item>As one of the world\'s leading international financial
            centers, Hong Kong has a major capitalist service economy
            characterized by low taxation and free trade, and the
            currency, Hong Kong dollar, is the ninth most traded
            currency in the world.</item>
        <item>Indonesia comprises 17,508 islands.Three of the ten
            largest islands in the world are found here.The biggest
            island in Indonesia is Sumatra.</item>
        <item>The Isle of Man is a self-governing British Crown
            Dependency, located in the Irish Sea between the islands of
            Great Britain and Ireland, within the British Isles. The
            island has been inhabited since before 6500 BC and now is a
            home to 80,058 people</item>
        <item>Hong Kong has more Rolls Royce’s per person than any other
            city in the world.</item>
        <item>The word “Bhutan” translates to “Land of the Thunder
            Dragon.” It earned the nickname because of the fierce storms
            that often roll in from the Himalayas.</item>
        <item>Djibouti is the 3rd smallest country on the African
            continent, after The Gambia and Swaziland. As of 2005,
            Djibouti has the least number of people on the African
            continent.</item>
        <item>Greenland is the largest non-continental island in the
            world with an area of 2,166,086 sq. km.</item>
        <item>Jersey has numerous residents born outside Jersey; 47%% of
            the population are not native to the island. The total
            population is nearly 88,000. Thirty percent of the
            population is concentrated in Saint Helier, the island\'s
            only town.</item>
        <item>According to the World Tourism and Trade Council 2004
            report, Montenegro is the fastest growing tourist
            destination in the World.</item>
        <item>With 5,637 kilometers of coastline and more than 1,518
            islands, Panama has more beaches than one can imagine. No
            wonder it is among the top retirement locations in the
            world.</item>
        <item>French is the official language in Senegal, but really
            only used regularly by a minority of Senegalese who were
            educated in colonial-style schools of French origin. Most
            people speak their own ethnic language.</item>
        <item>According to historians, Damascus, the capital of Syria,
            is the oldest inhabited city in the world as it has
            continuous been inhabited for more than 4,000 years.</item>
        <item>The national flag of Jordan shows equally spaced,
            horizontal bands of black, white, and green, with a red
            triangle at the hoist. In the center of the red triangle,
            there is a seven point white star, the points representing
            the seven opening verses of the Koran.</item>
        <item>Kazakhstan has the main launch site for Soviet and Russian
            space exploration at Baikonur, the world\'s oldest and
            largest operational space launch facility.</item>
        <item>There are 70 tribes in Kenya. The Kikuyu tribe is the
            biggest with 20%% of the population.</item>
        <item>In the last 30 years, the temperature of the water in
            Kuwait Bay has increased by .6 degrees per decade. This is
            three times faster than the global average rate.</item>
        <item>The flag of Kyrgyzstan displays a tunduk (seen from
            below), the crown of a yurt, the traditional nomadic house
            of the Kyrgyz people.</item>
        <item>The Plain of Jars in Laos is home to nearly thousands of
            huge stone jars, each of which is large enough to hold a
            person. The largest jar weighs over six tons! Estimated at
            about 2,000 years old, the purpose of the jars along with
            their makers is still a mystery.</item>
        <item>Official language in Latvia is Latvian. It’s not Russian,
            not even similar. But there are lot of Russian speaking
            people in Latvia, that’s why the mistaken suggestion that
            “all Latvians speak Russian” or “Latvians are Russians”.
        </item>
        <item>Lebanon is the country that has the most books written
            about it.</item>
        <item>Lesotho is the only constitutional monarchy in Africa. The
            current king is His Majesty King Letsie III who was crowned
            for the second time in 1996, having briefly ruled in place
            of his father during a constitutional crisis prior to that.
        </item>
        <item>Liberia was one of the more stable African countries until
            the civil war broke out in 1989, which witnessed the brutal
            massacre of over 200,000 Liberians across seven years.
        </item>
        <item>The Libyan Desert covers most of Libya. It is very arid
            and, in some places, it only rains once ever 10 or more
            years!</item>
        <item>Liechtenstein upholds a stance of military neutrality, and
            remains one of the few countries in the world to not have a
            Defense Force. Other such countries include Andorra and
            Costa Rica.</item>
        <item>By the end of the fourteenth century, Lithuania
            was the
            largest country in Europe.</item>
        <item>Luxembourg is the least populated country in the European
            Union, with only 465,000 inhabitants. It is also the 20th
            smallest of all the 194 independent countries in the world.
        </item>
        <item>After Las Vegas, Macau is one of the biggest gambling
            areas in the world. In fact, gambling is even legalized in
            Macau.</item>
        <item>Ninety percent of the plants and animals found on the
            island of Madagascar evolved there and nowhere else.</item>
        <item>The origin of the name Malawi remains unclear; it is held
            to be either derived from that of southern tribes, or noting
            the "glitter of the sun rising across the lake" (as seen in
            its flag).</item>
        <item>Malaysia is home to 14,500 species of flowering plants and
            trees, more than 200 species of mammals, 600 species of
            bids, 140 species of snakes and 60 species of lizards.
        </item>
        <item>In 2008 Maldives was ranked second as the best country
            brand for natural beauty and third as best country brand for
            resort and lodging options.</item>
        <item>Kids in Mali only go to school for 2 years.</item>
        <item>There are over 350 churches on the Maltese islands. Many
            were built in the seventeenth century, making them sights to
            behold even for non-believers. With their bell towers and
            domes, the churches are an integral part of the Maltese
            skyline.</item>
        <item>It is a known fact that the Marshall Islands comprise two
            parallel island groups. However, only a few people are aware
            of the fact that the island groups are called the Ratak
            Chain and the Ralik Chain. The name Ratak translates to
            sunrise and the name Ralik translates to sunset.</item>
        <item>Mauritania was one of the last countries in the world to
            officially abolish slavery. It passed a law prohibiting
            slavery in 1981. Slavery in Mauritania was mainly by
            Mauritanian Arabs enslaving indigenous black Mauritanians.
        </item>
        <item>Mauritius is one of the leading tourist destinations in
            Africa, receiving about 7000,000 visitors with some of the
            finest beach in the Indian ocean such as Grand Bay,
            Pereybere, Belle Mare, Blue Bay, La Morne and Tamarin and
            Flic en Flac, Mauritius makes for an idyllic tropical
            holiday.</item>
        <item>The name Micronesia derives from the Greek mikros, meaning
            small, and nesos, meaning island. The term was first
            proposed to distinguish the region in 1831 by Jules Dumont
            d\'Urville.</item>
        <item>Moldova is better known for its wines. For many
            years, the
            general occupation of majority of people in the
            country was
            related to wine making and viticulture. The major and
            well-established industry in this country is none other than
            the wine industry. The country has vineyard area of 360,000
            acres.</item>
        <item>The Grimaldi family has ruled for more than 600 years
            before Monaco officially became a sovereign state. The royal
            family name comes from its Genoese founder, Grimaldo.</item>
        <item>In Mongolia there are 13 times more horses than people.
        </item>
        <item>Montserrat is known as the Emerald Isle of the Caribbean.
            In recent years the island has experienced extensive
            volcanic activity and in 1995 the eruption of the Sourfriere
            Hills volcano forced mass exodus from Montserrat.</item>
        <item>Morocco is situated in North Africa and it is the only
            African country that is presently not a member of the
            ‘African Union’.</item>
        <item>In 2002, a severe drought hit many central and southern
            parts of the country, including previously flood-stricken
            areas. Poverty remains widespread, with more than 50%% of
            Mozambicans living on less than $1 a day.</item>
        <item>The capital of Namibia is Windhoek. The name Windhoek is
            of Dutch origin meaning \'corner of wind\'. Windhoek is
            located on Namibia central high plateau region.</item>
        <item>Nauru has no capital and is the world\'s only independent
            republic not to have one. Yaren is the island\'s largest
            city with about 1,200 people.</item>
        <item>There are eight peaks with a total of 19 points above 8000
            metres in Nepal.</item>
        <item>The nickel boom in the 1960\'s helped New Caledonia grow
            very rapidly. New Caledonia also has 25%% of the world\'s
            nickel reserves, most of which is traded with France and
            Japan.</item>
        <item>Nicaragua is larger then Ireland and Portugal put
            together.</item>
        <item>Niger obtained its independence from France in 1960 after
            50 years of rule. Niger has continued to rely heavily on
            France for economic support.</item>
        <item>Niue, one of the world\'s largest coral atolls, is
            approximately 1500 miles northeast of New Zealand.</item>
        <item>In North Korea you can’t turn off the government radio
            installed in your home, only reduce the volume.</item>
        <item>In the past, Oman used to be one of the richest countries
            in the world, with the wealth mainly originating from the
            incense trade.</item>
        <item>Pakistan has the second largest Muslim population in the
            world. It is second to Indonesia.</item>
        <item>Even though shirts and other forms of clothing are widely
            used in the islands, the traditional local women still go
            topless inside their homes - some do so around their
            village.</item>
        <item>There are more than 800 different languages spoken in
            Papua New Guinea</item>
        <item>Paraguay got it’s independence in 1811, may the 14th.
            Before it was colonized by the Spanish, the land was ruled
            by an old tribe, which called it self, the Guarani.</item>
        <item>The Philippines is the world\'s 3rd largest
            English-speaking nation, next to the USA and the UK.</item>
        <item>Puerto Rico, also known as the \'Island of Enchantment\'
            comprises an archipelago that includes the main Puerto Rico
            island and other small islands. The Puerto Rico archipelago
            is 100 miles long by 35 miles wide and is inhabited with
            over 3.9 million people.</item>
        <item>Sheikh Hamad bin Khalifa Al Thani is the current ruling
            Emir of the State of Qatar. According to Forbes, he became
            ruler in 1995 after ousting his father in a bloodless coup,
            and is worth an estimated $2 billion.</item>
        <item>Rwanda is the most densely populated country in Africa.
        </item>
        <item>Saint Helena named after St Helena of Constantinople, is
            an island of volcanic origin in the South Atlantic Ocean. he
            British used the island as a place of exile, most notably
            for Napoleon I, Dinuzulu kaCetshwayo and more than 5,000
            Boer prisoners.</item>
        <item>Saint Kitts and Nevis is the smallest sovereign state in
            the Americas, in both area and population.</item>
        <item>St. Lucia is an island state located in the Caribbean Sea.
            The island was formed as the result of volcanic activity and
            is just 27 miles long and 14 miles across at the point of
            maximum width.</item>
        <item>As a part of the Netherlands Antilles and the Kingdom of
            the Netherlands, St. Maarten boasts 77 different
            nationalities.</item>
        <item>Saint Pierre and Miquelon is a group of small French
            islands in the North Atlantic Ocean, the main islands being
            Saint Pierre and Miquelon, south of the Canadian province of
            Newfoundland and Labrador.</item>
        <item>The tourism industry has won St. Vincent and the
            Grenadines the Best Sailing &amp; Yachting Island of The
            Year award for the year 2009.</item>
        <item>Samoans are known throughout Polynesia as the "happy
            people" because of their enjoyment of life and their
            good-spirited nature.</item>
        <item>San Marino is the world\'s oldest republic. According to
            tradition, it was founded by a Christian stonemason named
            Marino in 301 A.D.</item>
        <item>Sao Tome and Principe is Africas smallest state and
            situated in the gulf of Guinea in western Africa.</item>
        <item>Seychelles granite islands are the oldest islands in the
            world. They are different from Mauritius and Reunion
            Islands. The latter are volcanic while Seychelles is made of
            ancient granite.</item>
        <item>On February 14, 1972, Sierra Leone made headlines when the
            world\'s third-largest gem-quality diamond – called the
            "Star of Sierra Leone" – was discovered in Koidu.</item>
        <item>Symbolism of the National Flag: Red symbolizes universal
            brotherhood and equality of man while white signifies purity
            and virtue. The crescent moon represents a young nation on
            the rise and the five stars signify the ideals of democracy,
            peace, progress, justice and equality.</item>
        <item>90%% of Slovaks have completed at least secondary
            education - the highest score in the EU (along with Poles,
            Czechs, and Slovenes).</item>
        <item>The Slovenian language is one of the most archaic
            languages in Europe and in the world. It is the only EU
            official language which has the Dual. In addition, it has
            the most dialects given the number of inhabitants.</item>
        <item>The Solomon Islands are a remote and unspoilt travel
            destination, with a slowly developing tourist industry. The
            superb marine life in the surrounding waters makes the
            islands an excellent destination for diving</item>
        <item>Somalia has one of the lowest HIV infection rates in
            Africa, but close to 35%% of all children born in Somalia
            die before they are five years old due to disease and
            dehydration.</item>
        <item>South Africa is the second largest exporter of fruit in
            the world.</item>
        <item>South Georgia is a remote and inhospitable collection of
            islands, consisting of South Georgia and a chain of smaller
            islands, the South Sandwich Islands.</item>
        <item>The Sri Lankan flag is the only one in the world to
            recognize different religious groups. The yellow border and
            pipul leaves symbolise Buddhism which is the main religion
            in the country. As well as this the green and saffron bands
            represent the country’s Muslim and Hindu Tamil communities.
        </item>
        <item>A girl born in southern Sudan has a better chance of dying
            during pregnancy or childbirth than of completing primary
            school.</item>
        <item>Suriname is the smallest sovereign state in South America.
            The former name of Suriname is Nederland Guyana or
            Netherlands Guiana or Dutch Guiana.</item>
        <item>Polygamy is an accepted part of Swaziland\'s tradition and
            is still legal (but very rarely practiced today).</item>
        <item>Taiwan is sometimes called “Ilha Formosa,” which means
            “beautiful island” in Portuguese. Portuguese sailors gave
            Taiwan this name in the sixteenth century.</item>
        <item>The civil war in Tajikistan began in 1992 with protesters
            who were against the presidential elections and who felt
            they were not fairly represented in the country. On June 26,
            1997, the two sides came to an agreement and a peace accord
            was signed, ending the fighting. Over 50,000 were estimated
            to have been killed during the war.</item>
        <item>One in ten Tanzanians is living with HIV/AIDS. The crisis
            has left nearly 1 million children orphaned.</item>
        <item>The Orchid is Thailand’s best flowering export. Exports of
            the Orchid are valued at US$250million per annum.</item>
        <item>According to the Constitution of the Democratic Republic
            of Timor Leste, the yellow triangle represents "the traces
            of colonialism in East Timor\'s History"; the black triangle
            represents "the obscurantism that needs to be overcome"; the
            red base of the flag represents "the struggle for national
            liberation"; whilst the star, or "the light that guides", is
            white to represent peace.</item>
        <item>5.5 million people live in Togo. Life expectancy is around
            57 years. Birth rate is on average 5 children per woman.
            Literacy rate is just over 60%%.</item>
        <item>Tonga is an archipelago of 172 islands in the South
            Pacific, most of which are uninhabited, covering an area of
            7700 sq km (3000 sq miles).</item>
        <item>Tobago was the location of the book "Robinson Crusoe" by
            Daniel Defoe, and is also believed to be the place Robert
            Louis Stevenson had in mind when he wrote Treasure Island.
        </item>
        <item>Tunisia has served as a popular location for some of
            Hollywood\'s biggest films, among which include Star wars,
            Jesus of Nazareth, The English Patient and Raiders of the
            Lost Ark.</item>
        <item>Turkmenistan possesses the world\'s fourth largest
            reserves of natural gas resources. Although it is wealthy in
            natural resources in certain areas, most of the country is
            covered by the Karakum (Black Sand) Desert.</item>
        <item>Tuvalu formerly known as the Ellice Islands, is a
            Polynesian island nation located in the Pacific Ocean,
            midway between Hawaii and Australia. Its nearest neighbors
            are Kiribati, Nauru, Samoa and Fiji. It comprises four reef
            islands and five true atolls.</item>
        <item>About half the population in Uganda live on less that
            US$1.25 per day.</item>
        <item>The United Arab Emirates consists of seven states, termed
            emirates (because they are ruled by emirs), which are Abu
            Dhabi, Ajman, Dubai, Fujairah, Ras al-Khaimah, Sharjah and
            Umm al-Quwain.</item>
        <item>The largest note in Uzbekistan is 1000 sym, which is worth
            about 0.60 EUR. Changing foreign currency inevitably leaves
            you with impressive stacks of notes to carry around, making
            wallets all but useless.</item>
        <item>Vanuatu is one of the most diverse countries in the world.
            The word "Vanuatu" means \'Land Eternal\', so apt for this
            beautiful, unspoilt paradise.</item>
        <item>Venezuela has had more Miss Universes and Miss Worlds than
            any other country.</item>
        <item>Vietnam is shaped like a narrow \'S\'. Even though Vietnam
            is 1,650 kilometers (1,031 miles) from north to south, the
            country gets as narrow as 50 kilometers (31 miles) across.
        </item>
        <item>Tourism is Virgin Islands\' primary industry in the
            islands in terms of both economics and employment. There are
            over 2 million visitors per year.</item>
        <item>Yemen\'s border countries are Saudi Arabia and Oman. A
            short stretch of sea separates it from Djibouti. The
            country\'s population is roughly about 21 million.</item>
        <item>Just over 11 million people live in Zambia. Life
            expectancy is around 39 years. Birth rate is on average 5.47
            per woman. 16.5%% of the population is believed to have
            HIV/AIDS.</item>
        <item>The name Zimbabwe derives from “Dzimba dza mabwe,” meaning
            “great houses of stone” in the Shona language.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
